A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
So you've come.
Here you are. It's about time.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Mifune.
Right, now let's do this thing.
One win, one loss so far. This'll be the decisive battle.
That's right. I'll show you who the winner is once and for all.
Subaki, you ready to go?
Yes.
Before you lies the path of the demon and the path of the warrior.
Tell me, Blackstar, which of these two paths are you going to follow?
I'm falling, coming to my shadow.
息をひきそめて待っている.
The dream life.
Don't scare me.
君が望めば
どんな世界も
その目に映せるから
I'll see you in your dreams, yeah, baby.
怖い夢だとしても
天づる君のために
星を砕ぎ
飾り付けた
Black paper
信じてくれたなら
We knew
No see you are young
Forever with your soul
見上げれば
輝く
月のように
I can't help but wonder if handing over this magic tool is the right thing to do.
What is dad planning?
If he's after all these tools for some sinister purpose,
I'll have to act.
Hey, kid, you should see this.
What, Patty?
There!
I wonder what it is.
Forever with your soul
Warrior or slaughterer?
Showdown.
Mifune vs. Blackstar?
Forever with your soul
How does it look out there, Azusa?
I hate to say it, but not very good.
Our forces on the front line are advancing,
but they've got a long way to go before they reach the castle.
Forever with your soul
And the relay stations?
What's the situation there?
Forever with your soul
Well, we've succeeded in taking three of the six.
The stations in the Middle East, Europe, and Oceania are under our control.
They are no longer operational.
However, the fight continues at the other three stations.
Forever with your soul
Destroying those won't be enough.
We'd only delay the spread of the madness, not stop it.
You're right about that.
Until we defeat the Kishin itself, our victory will be incomplete.
Forever with your soul
Oh, Lord Death.
Hm?
Fool!
It's Kid.
He's returned.
And the magic tool?
He succeeded in retrieving it.
Well, some good news finally.
Tell him to find Joe in the secret vault and wait for further instructions.
Hey, Kid, do you recognize this place?
Yeah.
The so-called contractors working in there.
This strange key in the Academy's recent secrecy.
I know they're hiding something.
And the answer is behind this door.
In our earlier fights, I thought I'd sense some potential at you.
I guess I was wrong about that.
Arrogant fool underestimating me now could be bad for your health.
Subaki! Ninja sword mode, right?
Let's go!
Here I am!
He's fast.
Your soul resonance has gotten faster than before.
You're soul resonance has gotten faster than before.
I suppose you have improved since the last time.
But are you fast enough?
Infinite sword style.
Get ready.
I see through your disguise.
The real one is there.
You are alive.
You have sharp eyes.
Dodgeon kept you alive this time.
I thought I'd say no fun.
The real one is there.
It's not a scary one.
Horizontal line attack.
One!
Two!
Horizontal line attack.
Are you okay?
Patetic.
It's barely a scratch.
You have sharp eyes.
Dodgeon kept you alive this time.
I thought this would happen.
I have to use the enchanted sword.
You did a great job, kid.
Thanks for taking on that mission for your old man.
Hi there, cutie.
The magic tool, please.
Here it is.
Before I hand it over, I want to know everything that's been going on.
What exactly does this magic tool do?
And why do you want it?
Oh, all right.
Whoa, hold on a second. You've been so secretive and so dodgy.
And now you're going to tell me just because I asked what's going on here.
I don't understand. Why would you do...
Sorry about that.
But we really couldn't let just anybody know what we were doing.
It had to be a secret operation.
You get it?
We had to make sure our plan was kept from Arachne and the Kishin.
Oh, really?
So then we've been suspicious for no reason?
We're pretty stupid, huh?
But now, we've got the magic tool in our hands.
So we can afford to be a bit more open.
Okay, so tell me what it does, then.
This little guy was Abon's final creation.
You see, Abon is the last magic tool.
And now, we'll be careful not to make sense.
So now it's going.
And we'll make sure we PBK on my mind.
So now I'm taking a moment of the hp.
Well, plan says we go in there.
But what do we do?
Just march right in?
I don't know.
Our orders were simply to infiltrate the castle.
And so we will.
These should make it a bit easier.
Advance!
The castle isn't far now.
Let's move.
Advance!
Damn, DWMA.
They're doing better than I thought.
Mosquito.
What is taking you so long?
Forgive me, my lady.
It's a tougher fight than expected.
All right, then.
Time for the secret weapon.
Are you sure about this, Lady Arachne?
Our own soldiers are still within range.
Do it anyway.
As you wish.
And so, it comes to this in the end, does it?
One shot from this should be all we need to win the day.
I mean, this weapon will decimate the enemy and anything else in its path.
Prepare yourselves for utter devastation.
What's that?
Now, while he's distracted.
Tsubaki, enchanted sword mode.
Got it.
With the sorry state you're in, you won't last much longer.
Don't worry.
I plan on making this quick.
Let's go!
Go, Resonance!
Shadow's war!
Such anger and malice.
Is it the path of the demon, then?
I'll defeat you.
Nothing else matters to me.
Think hard before you say that.
You still have a chance to choose the right path.
Shut up!
I don't need advice from you!
Those eyes, they look familiar.
What the hell's that?
What do you know?
No one ever told me the castle could move!
It's been a long time,
Great Wizard Abon.
It's been a long time.
That means Dad and Abon do know each other.
Yes, Lord Death.
Sorry, but we don't have time to catch up.
I want you to lend me Brew's power.
Why do you need Brew?
Well, thanks to the Kishan and that spider witch,
we're in a bit of a pickle.
Asherah and Arachne?
Father.
Tell me how you and Abon know each other.
That's a good question.
I guess it might be helpful if I explain some of our history.
It's been a long time,
but Abon and I used to fight side by side.
He was a member of my elite guard squadron.
He knew the Kishan, Ashura, well.
It's hard to believe now, but they were comrades once.
If he was one of yours, then why did he create the magic tools?
Well, there was a lot going on back then.
What a great explanation, thank you.
How should I put it?
Well, he always loved playing with machines.
Yes, very helpful.
Oh, jeez.
Well...
His original goal was to preserve and protect order in the world.
That's why he began his research into magic tools.
Obviously, for any object of great power,
there are always those who are willing to risk anything to obtain that power.
And, of course, the more powerful the object is,
the greater the danger of it falling into the wrong hands.
Abon knew all this, but he had faith in humanity,
so he continued his research nonetheless.
Eventually, his work took on a more narrow focus.
He began studying one area exclusively.
It became an obsession.
What area was that?
Immortality.
What kind of greeting is that?
No!
What's Excalibur doing here?
Why wouldn't I be here?
Him again?
Oh, the funny alien guy.
This should be interesting.
It was not idle curiosity that led to Abon's immortality research.
Indeed, the true reason is much more tragic.
His wife lay dying.
Abon's obsession with immortality was born because he desperately sought to save his beloved.
But no matter how great the inventor or how noble the cause, transcending death is an impossible feat.
Not even Abon could hope to succeed in such an endeavor.
But when all seemed lost, someone appeared by his side, offering help and comforting words.
That someone was...
The Witch Arachne.
Come on, is this guy for real?
I can't be sure.
It's a heart-rending tale.
But what if it's nothing but another manipulation?
I assure you, it's not.
Huh?
Abon and Arachne joined forces.
They combined his research into immortality with her research on magic weapons.
And from that, the magic tool Brew came into being.
Long ago, I met a man whose eyes looked exactly like yours do now.
He bore the same star tattoo as well.
He showed no mercy, even to those who deserved it.
You, your StarClan.
You're close to forsaking the path of the warrior for the path of the demon.
Oh, please.
What use do I have for paths?
I'm here to win, plain and simple.
That's all that matters.
It's not too late.
Stop while you can.
That's enough.
I'm done listening.
Yeah, that's a great story, Samurai.
But why should I care about some dumb clan that got itself wiped out?
Because the child of a demon is a demon as well.
Your path has been decided for you.
Shut up!
You have the strength to be so much more.
So why this?
There's nothing greater in this life than winning.
Victory's always the path I choose.
You're wielding a double-edged sword.
It may kill your opponents, but it's cutting your soul as well.
White Star.
He was the first man I ever truly feared.
But feared as he was, he was not fearless himself.
The thought that he might one day be defeated made him tremble.
It shook him to the very depths of his soul.
Man, for a samurai, you sure talk a lot.
You're different, though.
You've already tasted defeat, haven't you?
What did you say?
He strayed from the path for a reason.
Perhaps you should hear it before you decide.
All right, White Star.
Let's end this.
Your eyes.
You aren't even human anymore, are you?
He couldn't conquer the darkness inside himself.
What about you?
Will you fight that darkness, or will you become a demon, too?
I'm not gonna lose.
He was defeated because he was weak.
I'll show you.
I'm stronger than him!
You foolish boy.
He wasn't weak.
No matter what, he always had to push harder, reach higher.
He never knew when to stop.
Because of that...
The what?
He lost himself.
The warrior became a demon.
I'll ask you again.
Which path will you follow?
That of the warrior, or of the demon?
Shut up, samurai.
You don't know what you're talking about.
You're nothing but a fool if you think you can order me around.
You've chosen the demon.
I can do nothing more for you.
Blackstar!
How delicious this power is.
Reduce them to lumps of flesh.
You have a habit of popping up at unexpected times, Excalibur.
Why are you here now?
Did you come to see Abon?
Ha!
That's just a bonus.
My reason goes a great deal deeper than that.
Oh.
You're here to help us out, then.
Fool!
That isn't it.
I've come to observe.
Now, let's begin.
Baru, unlock.
Baru, even.
itätenkas
Baru, unlock.
Thank you.
Weapons locked and loaded.
All system lights are green.
Lord Death, we're ready.
Good.
Death City Robot, fight mode.
Transform.
Ta-da!
Well, that was a fun game, Azusa.
But does this thing actually transform?
Of course it doesn't.
On the next episode of Soul Eater,
the miraculous coffee table flip,
fly.
Our Death City Robot.
I told you, it doesn't transform.
Oh, really?